A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Educational Interests, Series G FA316
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Schools
  - Schools - Pineland College, 1930-1941 (Box 35, Folder 235)
    Appeals for aid. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Thomas B. Appleget.
    175P5
  - Schools - Power Memorial Academy, 1946-1954 (Box 35, Folder 236)
    Laurance S. Rockefeller contributes $500 towards gymnasium at school. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard.
    175P6
  - Schools - Professional Children's School, 1929-1961 (Box 36, Folder 237)
    Work of school with talented children active in the theater, radio, television, or other arts. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributions; John D. Rockefeller 3rd contributions. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    175P7
  - Schools - Professional Children's School - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Pledge, February 1930 (Box 36, Folder 238)
  - Schools - Professional Children's School - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Pledge, March 1931 (Box 36, Folder 239)
  - Schools - Professional Children's School - Contributions, 1933-1961 (Box 36, Folder 240)
    By John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, and Mary French Rockefeller.
  - Schools - Piney Woods School, 1942-1961 (Box 36, Folder 241)
    Appeals for aid; all declined. Correspondents include Mary Mills.
    175P8
  - Schools - Phillips Exeter Academy - Rockefeller Contributions to Music Building, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 242)
    Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, and John D. Rockefeller 3rd give $200,000 towards cost of new music building. Correspondents include Dana S. Creel, David Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    175P9
  - Schools - Phillips Exeter Academy - Rockefeller Contributions to Music Building, 1959-1960 (Box 36, Folder 242A)
  - Schools - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1946-1961 (Box 36, Folder 243)
    Contributions by John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller. Correspondents include William Saltonstall, Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Schools - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1956-1958 (Box 36, Folder 243A)
  - Schools - Rabun Gap-Nacoochee School, 1920-1941 (Box 36, Folder 244)
    Rabun Gap a unique farm school for poor mountain whites; received contributions from John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1920, 1924; his 1925 conditional pledge cancelled and replaced with larger pledge in 1927 aiding merger of Rabun Gap and Nacoochee schools. Religious cooperation problem after merger. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s 1937 contribution to endowment fund, 1939 contribution to retirement fund for Ritchies. Some printed material describing school. Correspondents include A. J. Ritchie, Rev. J. H. Hargreaves, Willard S. Richardson, Thomas B. Appleget.
    175R
  - Schools - Rabun Gap-Nacoochee School - Contributions, 1920-1939 (Box 36, Folder 245)
    Total $81,000.
  - Schools - Riverdale Country School, 1937-1958 (Box 37, Folder 246)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declines to participate in school's 1937 expansion program. Nelson A. Rockefeller's $1,000 contribution to 1945 property purchase (Rodman Rockefeller attended for a year). Declination of further appeals to develop a "world" school with an international student body. Correspondents include Charles Keppell, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard, Willard S. Richardson, F. S. Hackett.
    175R1
  - Schools - Rhode Island School of Design, 1938-1961 (Box 37, Folder 247)
    Lucy Truman Aldrich and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller interested. 1951-1956 David Rockefeller and Nelson A. Rockefeller contributions to Abby Aldrich Rockefeller memorial rooms in school's art museum. Later appeals declined. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel, William Edwards.
    175R2
  - Schools - Rhode Island School of Design, 1938-1961 (Box 37, Folder 0247A)
    Lucy Aldrich Rockefeller and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller interested. 1951-1956 David Rockefeller and Nelson A. Rockefeller contributions to Abby Aldrich Rockefeller memorial rooms in school's art museum. Later appeals declined. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel, William Edwards.
  - Schools - Rockland Country Day School, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 248)
    Description of school and its aims; Laurance S. Rockefeller 1961 nonrecurring contribution. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel, Charles Frankel.
    175R4
  - Schools - Shanghai American School, 1922-1940 (Box 37, Folder 249)
    School for American and European children in China. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s nonrecurring conditional pledge, 1930. Later appeals declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, Arthur Woods, Raymond B. Fosdick, Willard Barlett.
    175S
  - Schools - Scarborough School, 1941-1961 (Box 37, Folder 250)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd's interest in school's "Work Program," his 1946 and 1949 nonrecurring contributions. John D. Rockefeller 3rd's son attended school; John D. Rockefeller 3rd's advice on financing independent schools. David Rockefeller's nonrecurring anonymous contribution, 1960; John D. Rockefeller 3rd 1960 contribution. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Charles Tillinghast, Jonathan Bingham, Mrs. F. Vanderlip.
    175S1
  - Schools - Scarborough School, 1960-1961 (Box 37, Folder 0250A)
  - Schools - School of American Ballet, 1937-1950 (Box 37, Folder 251)
    Correspondence between Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, L. Kirstein, and E. M. Warburg. Nelson A. Rockefeller anonymous contribution, 1937; Nelson A. Rockefeller acts as patron of 1937 performance produced by School. Printed materials. Correspondents include Lincoln Kirstein, Nelson A. Rockefeller, S. M. Warburg.
    175S2
  - Schools - School of Design in Chicago, 1939-1943 (Box 37, Folder 252)
    Nelson A. Rockefeller declines to contribute or become life member, 1939. David Rockefeller became life member, 1941. Correspondents include Walter Paepeke, David Rockefeller, Nelson Rockefeller, L. Moholy-Nagy.
    175S3
  - Schools - Salem School - Kurt Hahn Project, 1940-1949 (Box 37, Folder 253)
    Mr. Hahn's attempt to "rescue" European youth, especially post-war German students, through establishment of special schools in Germany and Great Britain which would develop the "service motive." John D. Rockefeller 3rd and David Rockefeller interested (John D. Rockefeller 3rd gifts, 1950 and 1952); Rockefeller Foundation grant for German exchange students; support of United States High Commissioner for Germany, McCloy. Printed materials on Hahn Project, Gordonstown School, and articles and reports by Hahn. Declinations of later appeals. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard, Kurt Hahn, John McCloy, Robert Bates, Christian Herter.
    175S4
  - Schools - Salem School - Kurt Hahn Project, 1950-1958 (Box 37, Folder 0253A)
  - Schools - Salem School - Kurt Hahn Project, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 0253B)
  - Schools - Sidwell Friends School, 1950-1961 (Box 38, Folder 254)
    175S5
  - Schools - Sleepy Hollow High School, 1955-1960 (Box 38, Folder 255)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution to purchase of site and construction of building. Declination of invitations; gifts to Parent Teacher Association (PTA). Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dana S. Creel.
    175S6
  - Schools - Thessalonica Agricultural and Industrial Institute, 1924-1961 (Box 38, Folder 256)
    Abby Aldrich Rockefeller contributions to farm school in Greece; David Rockefeller's annual contribution after 1940 ($2,500 a year). Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel.
    175T5
  - Schools - Thessalonica Agricultural and Industrial Institute, 1941-1955 (Box 38, Folder 0256A)
  - Schools - Thessalonica Agricultural and Industrial Institute, 1956-1962 (Box 38, Folder 0256B)
  - Schools - Training School, Vineland, New Jersey, 1941-1959 (Box 38, Folder 257)
    School for mentally disabled children; all requests declined. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
    175T6
  - Schools - Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute, 1899-1922 (Box 38, Folder 258)
    John D. Rockefeller's contributions to Institute; tribute to Booker T. Washington. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s 1925 contribution to Tuskegee and Hampton Institute joint drive. Personal gift to Robert Maton. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s continuing interest in school. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Frederick T. Gates, Arthur W. Packard, R. R. Maton, Booker T. Washington.
    175T9
  - Schools - Tuskegee Institute, Alabama, 1922-1936 (Box 38, Folder 259)
    Formerly the Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute. John D. Rockefeller's contributions to Institute; tribute to Booker T. Washington. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s 1925 contribution to Tuskegee and Hampton Institute joint drive. Personal gift to Robert Maton. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s continuing interest in school. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Frederick T. Gates, Arthur W. Packard, R. R. Maton, Booker T. Washington.
  - Schools - Tuskegee Institute, Alabama, 1937-1957 (Box 38, Folder 260)
  - Schools - Tuskegee Institute - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1953-1961 (Box 39, Folder 261)
    Formerly the Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute. John D. Rockefeller 3rd declined trusteeship; received fruit cake from students in Department of Dietetics for several years. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, L. H. Foster.
  - Schools - Tuskegee Institute - Ann Elliot, 1953-1959 (Box 39, Folder 0261A)
    Formerly the Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute. John D. Rockefeller 3rd assisted Miss Elliot in graduate work at Juilliard. Interest in her career.
  - Schools - Tuskegee Institute - George Washington Carver Foundation, 1942-1955 (Box 39, Folder 262)
    Formerly the Tuskegee Normal and Industrial Institute. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $100 in 1943; later requests declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard.
    175T91
  - Schools - Universal School of Handicraft, 1936-1951 (Box 39, Folder 263)
    School located in Rockefeller Center taught weaving, ceramics, painting, and similar handicrafts; appeals for aid declined. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, Edward Hall.
    175U
  - Schools - Virginia Military Institute - George C. Marshall Research Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 39, Folder 264)
    Kenneth Chorley suggests that John D. Rockefeller, Jr. underwrite the collection of General Marshall's records and memories. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gives $150,000. Martha Baird Rockefeller made additional gift in 1961.
    175V
  - Schools - Virginia Military Institute - George C. Marshall Research Foundation, 1960-1961 (Box 39, Folder 0264A)
  - Schools - Woodstock School, 1946-1961 (Box 39, Folder 265)
    Laurance S. Rockefeller made contributions and guaranteed a capital loan for the school at Chase Bank. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller and R. B. Marston.
    175W
  - Schools - Wiltwyck School for Boys, 1942-1961 (Box 39, Folder 266)
    Reform school for Protestant Negro boys. Contributions by John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Rockefeller Brothers. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, E. C. Carder.
    175W1
  - Schools - Wiltwyck School for Boys, 1942-1961 (Box 39, Folder 266A)
  - Schools - Yard School - Mrs. Mueller, 1936-1947 (Box 40, Folder 267)
    Nelson A. Rockefeller paid for renovation of play area for kindergarten attended by some of his children. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard.
    175Y
  - Schools - Dr. Monroe's Report on Schools for American Children in Foreign Lands, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 268)
    Survey made for Institute of Social and Religious Research on quality of foreign schools for American children. Correspondents include Paul Monroe.
    175.1
- Colleges
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 269)
    Coe College, Iowa, 1926 Colegio John W. Rockefeller, Cuba, 1958 Columbia College (Dubuque, Iowa), 1921 Georgian Court College, 1929 John Carroll University, 1929-1934 Lincoln Institute, Kentucky, 1933 North Carolina College for Women, 1925-1932 Ohio State University, 1920-1958 Randolph Macon, Virginia, 1919-1930 Rosary College, 1920 Saint Lawrence University, New York, 1925 Strasburg University, 1923
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 270)
    College of St. Elizabeth, 1919-1920 Drury College, Missouri, 1944-1947 *Franklin College, Indiana, 1892-1902 *Indiana University, 1902-1904 *MacMaster University, 1906-1911 Ottawa University, Kansas, 1902-1904
    Colleges marked with an asterisk (*) indicate Rockefeller family participation or a contribution to that college.
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 271)
    Alfred Holbrook College, Ohio, 1940 Blackstone College for Girls, Virginia, 1931-1939 Findlay College, Ohio, 1939 Georgetown College, Kentucky, 1902-1940 Hardin-Simmons University, Texas, 1921-1935 Hartwick College, New York, 1935-1938 Milligan College, Tennessee, 1929-1940 Muskingum College, 1935-1938 New Jersey College for Women, 1947 Ogelthorpe University, 1926-1938 Parsons College, Iowa, 1928-1939 Presbyterian College, South Carolina, 1939-1942 Southern Methodist University, Texas, 1931-1940 University of Texas, 1936 *Washington and Lee University, Virginia, 1902 West Virginia University, 1925-1940
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 272)
    Banks College, Pennsylvania, 1943 Brewster-Parker Junior College / Breuton-Purker Junior College, Georgia, 1947 Flora Macdonald College, 1938-1941 Girard College, Pennsylvania, 1946 Hardin College / Hardin-Simmons College, 1945-1946 Indiana Course of Religious Higher Education / Indiana Council of Religion in Higher Education, 1949 Lincoln University, Missouri, 1945 Louisiana State University, 1942 Madison College, Tennessee, 1942 Mills College, California, 1941-1946 Ogontz Junior College, Pennsylvania, 1945 Otterbein College, Ohio, 1944 Piedmont College, Georgia, 1937-1944 Presbyterian College, South Carolina, 1939-1942 Queens College, New York, 1946 Ricker Classical Institute / Ricker Junior College, 1946 Russell Sage College, New York, 1944 Saint Bernard College, Alabama, 1946 Susquehanna University, Pennsylvania, 1937-1944 Tennessee Wesleyan College, 1948 Texas Christian University: Brite College of the Bible, 1946 University of New Hampshire, 1941 University of Richmond, Virginia, 1945 Upsala College, New Jersey, 1944-1949 *Washington and Lee University, Virginia, 1902-1946 Westchester Community College, 1954-1958 William Jennings Bryan University, Tennessee, 1945
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 273)
    Abilene Christian College, Texas, 1947 Alabama College, 1947 American University, Washington, D. C., 1943-1949 Baltic University, Germany, 1948 Bob Jones College, Tennessee, 1927-1947 Brewton-Parker Junior College, 1947 Brooklyn College, 1947 Drury College, 1944-1947 Erskine College, South Carolina, 1947 Georgia Northern and Agricultural College, 1948 Grand Canyon College, 1955 International University of Arts for Peace, Washington, D. C., 1946-1948 Lasell/Larell Junior College, New York, 1948 Manhattanville College, 1948 Marietta College, Ohio, 1924-1946 Maryland State College, 1948 Mississippi College, 1941-1946 Providence College, Rhode Island, 1946-1947 Prudence College, Ohio, 1948 Reinhardt College, Georgia, 1948 Saint Joseph's, Maryland, 1947 University of Alaska, 1948 University of Pittsburgh, 1948 Upsala College, New Jersey, 1944-1949 Virginia Seminary in Alexandria, 1945-1948 Yonkers Junior College, New York, 1947
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 274)
    Caldwell College, New Jersey, 1949 Claflin University, South Carolina, 1948 Claremont College, California, 1954 Cornell College of Iowa, 1949 Elizabethtown College, Pennsylvania, 1949 Georgetown College, Kentucky, 1949 Incarnate Word College, Texas, 1949 Kenyon College, Ohio, 1942-1950 LeClerc College, Illinois, 1949 New London Junior College, Connecticut, 1949 Paul Smiths College, 1949 Prairie View Agricultural and Mechanical College, Texas, 1949 Rust College, Massachusetts, 1949 University of Minnesota, 1954 University of Wisconsin, 1949 Upsala College, New Jersey, 1949 Wesleyan Methodist College, South Carolina, 1949 William M. Rice Institute, Texas, 1949 Woman's Medical College of Pennsylvania, 1949 Youngstown College, 1949
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 0274A)
    College of Sacred Heart, Louisiana, 1949 Regis College, Colorado, 1948 University of Hollywood, California, 1949
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 275)
    Asheville-Biltmore College, North Carolina, 1951 *Bennett College, New York, 1949-1951 Bergen Junior College, 1951 Chicago College of Osteopathy, 1951 Christian Brothers College, Missouri, 1957 Consolidated University of North Carolina, 1950 Defiance College, 1951 Gallaudet College, Maine, 1951 Genessee Junior College, 1951 Hiram College, Ohio, 1932-1951 Lewis and Clark College, Oregon, 1951 Madison College, Virginia, 1950 Middlebury College, Vermont, 1951 Mundelein College, Illinois, 1951 Nebraska Wesleyan University, 1951 Northwest Nazarene College, Idaho, 1950 Pacific University, 1950 Pomona College, California, 1949 St. Bonaventure, New York, 1933-1950 Southwestern College, 1951 State Teachers College, Pennsylvania, 1951 Virginia Union University, 1931-1950
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 0275A)
    Bradley University, Minnesota, 1949-1951
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 276)
    Annhurst College, Connecticut, 1950 East Carolina Teachers College, North Carolina, 1950 George Washington University, Washington, D. C., 1950 Judson College, Alabama, 1943-1950 Lenoir Rhyne College, North Carolina, 1950 Maryville College, Tennessee, 1920-1950 Maunaolu Community College, Hawaii, 1950 Northeastern University, Massachusetts, 1946-1950 Seattle University, 1950 Stevens Institute of Technology, New Jersey, 1927-1950 Storer College, West Virginia, 1950 Titusville Junior College, Pennsylvania, 1950 University of Delaware, 1950
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 0276A)
    Elon College, North Carolina, 1950 University of the State of New York, 1943-1950
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 277)
    Albion College, Michigan, 1952 Bethel College, Kansas, 1952 Bridgewater College, Virginia, 1952-1958 Eden Theological Seminary, Missouri, 1952 Hamline University, Minnesota, 1952 Lafayette College, Pennsylvania, 1925-1952 Langston University, Oklahoma, 1952 Northeastern Junior College, Colorado, 1952 *Norwich University, Vermont, 1951 Oakwood College, Alabama, 1952 Packard Junior College, New York, 1952 Packer Collegiate Institute, New York, 1952 Pepperdine College, California, 1950-1952 Salem College, West Virginia, 1926-1952 Seattle Pacific College, Washington, 1952 Washington and Jefferson College, Pennsylvania, 1952 Wiley College, Texas, 1952
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 0277A)
    Gammon Theological Seminary, Georgia, 1930-1952
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 278)
    Black Mountain College, North Carolina, 1934-1954 *Christ the King Theological Seminary, Illinois, 1954 Claremont College, California, 1954 Jefferson Biblical College, Michigan, 1954 J ohnson C. Smith University, North Carolina, 1954 Michigan State College, 1953 Pittsburgh-Xenia Theological Seminary, 1954 St. Paul's College, Washington, D. C., 1954 St. Xavier College Auxiliary, Illinois, 1954-1956 Shurtleff College, Illinois, 1947-1954 University of Arizona, 1954 Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1950-1954 West Virginia State College Bulletin, 1954
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 0278A)
    Colorado Woman's College, 1945-1954
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 279)
    Arctic College, 1954 Assumption College, Massachusetts, 1953 Champlain College, New York, 1952 Chapman College, California, 1956 College of St. Joseph on the Rio Grande, 1954 Episcopal Theological Seminary, Texas, 1954 Goddard College, Vermont, 1954 Hope College, Michigan, 1953 Jesuit Seminaries, 1952-1953 Lehigh University, Pennsylvania, 1953 Montana State University, 1953 Oakland City College, Indiana, 1954 San Francisco State College, 1953 Sioux Falls College, South Dakota, 1934-1953 Trinity College, Connecticut, 1947-1953 University of Connecticut, 1954 University of Kentucky, 1954 University of Puerto Rico, 1952 University of the South, Tennessee, 1948-1953 Valparaiso University, 1954 Voorhees School and Junior College, South Carolina, 1953
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 42, Folder 0279A)
    University of the South, Tennessee, 1948-1953
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 280)
    Chapman College, 1956 Cornell University, New York, 1956 Furman University, South Carolina, 1956 National War College, Washington, D. C., 1956 North Central College, Illinois, 1951 Pacific Bible College, California, 1956 Paul Quinn College, Texas, 1955-1956 Rio Grande College, Ohio, 1956 Sacred Heart Junior College and Academy, North Carolina, 1956 St. John's University, New York, 1945-1956 St. Xavier College, Illinois, 1954-1956 University of the Americas, 1956 University of Houston, 1956 University of Miami, 1940-1956 Wabash College, 1956 Winona Lake School of Theology, Indiana, 1953-1956
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 0280A)
    Leland College, Louisiana, 1956 *Mar Thoma College, India, 1954-1956 North Central College, Illinois, 1956 University of Florida, 1952-1956
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 281)
    Christ College and Seminary, New York, 1955 College of New Rochelle, New York, 1955 Cumberland Presbyterian Junior College, Kentucky, 1955 Derkum University, California, 1948-1956 Earlham College, Indiana, 1948-1955 Eastern Mennonite College, Virginia, 1956 Edward Waters College, Florida, 1955 Freed-Hardeman College, Tennessee, 1952-1955 Grand Canyon College, Arizona, 1955 Howard Payne College, Texas, 1955 LaCrosse State College, Wisconsin, 1955 Lawrence College, Wisconsin, 1955 Redlands University, California, 1931-1955 Scarritt College, Tennessee, 1928-1956 Villanova University, Pennsylvania, 1955 Walter Hervey Junior College, New York, 1956 West Virginia Wesleyan College, 1955 Wheaton College, Illinois, 1955 William Carey College, Mississippi, 1950-1956 *William Jewell College, Missouri, 1903-1955
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 0281A)
    Collegium Hiroshima, Japan, 1955 University of Minnesota, 1954
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 282)
    Beaver College, Pennsylvania, 1940-1957 Carson-Newman College, Tennessee, 1950-1957 Duke University, North Carolina, 1941-1957 Iowa Wesleyan College, 1949-1957 Mary Hardin-Baylor College, 1957 North Carolina College for Negroes, 1931-1957 Wessington Springs College, South Dakota, 1957 Wilberforce University, Ohio, 1936-1957
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 0282A)
    Keuka College, New York, 1945-1947 Pembroke College, 1953-1957
  - Colleges - Miscellaneous (Box 43, Folder 283)